A comedy with everything on it.
Good Burger is a family, comedy film directed by Brian Robbins.
teens with summer jobs at Good Burger try to save their small restaurant when a
corporate giant burger franchise moves in across the street.
Ed, played by Kel Mitchell.
Dexter Reed, played by Kenan Thompson.
Mr. Wheat, played by Sinbad.
Otis, played by Abe Vigoda.
Monique, played by Shar Jackson.
Mr. Bailey, played by Dan Schneider.
Good Burger is a 1997 American teen comedy film
starring Kenan Thompson and Kel Mitchell.
It was directed by Brian Robbins, and written by Dan
Schneider with Kevin Kopelow and Heath Seifert.
The film is a spin-off of the "Good Burger" comedy sketch from the Nickelodeon
variety series All That, with Mitchell reprising his role as Ed.
The story follows Dexter Reed, a high school student who, in order to pay off the damages he made to his teacher's car, takes a summer job at the
titular fast food restaurant, where he and Ed, his dimwitted co-worker, stumble upon an evil plot by a rival fast-food restaurant.
The film was produced by Nickelodeon Movies and Tollin/Robbins
Productions, and was filmed from March to April 1997.
It premiered on July 19, 1997, and was released worldwide on
July 25 of the same year by Paramount Pictures.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and grossed $23.7 million.
In the years after its release, the film received a cult following.
A sequel titled Good Burger 2 was released on November 22, 2023, on Paramount+.
The film explores themes of competition, fast food
restaurant, nostalgic, burgers, hilarious.
The tone is lighthearted.